DAVID HARRISON SMITH

WEB DEVELOPER, PROJECT MANAGER

Download PDF

exmokie@gmail.com (717) - 497-0842

Summary

Obsessed with producing verifiably awesome code. Willing to learn and adapt to change. Leads teams in sales strategy and agile development. Speaks convincingly while expressing complex ideas in understandable terms.

Skills

Web Development

Loves to code in Python and develop strong databasecentered web applications.

Project Management S

Utilizes scrum workflow in an Agile Development workspace.

Sales

Sold 5 million dollars worth of product over two years.

Technical

Python	JavaScript	HTML
Django	AngularJS	CSS
PostgreSQL	jQuery	Karma

Experience

Coding Campus

Python and Django Apprenticeship

March 2015-Present

Developed multiple test-driven projects utilizing the Django and AngularJS frameworks. Ongoing projects may be viewed at www.davidharrisonsmith.com, and are updated often.

Toyota Motor Corporation

2013-2015

Sales and Leasing Consultant

Offered bug fixes and user experience recommendations for SNAP21 application. Assisted with integration of Dealersocket CRM for the dealership and helped train employees on utilization.

New Roads Behavioral Health

2011-2012

Residential Program Manager

Doubled revenue in 6 months by bringing drug testing in-house and making facilities JCAHO compliant. Assisted the IT Manager with troubleshooting in the network. Served as company liaison for the BestNotes CRM.

IT Department at BYU

2010-2011

Language Analyst

Constructed and organzized the database for the Hungarian version of the LDS scriptures online.

Education

Brigham Young University - Provo, Utah BA in Ancient Near Eastern Studies — **3.63 GPA**